Wake up in the mornin'
迎来新的一天
And I pull the covers over my head
我却拉起被子蒙上眼
Hey-oh
Week is starting, week is starting
又到周一 又到周一
I gotta get it movin'
虽已到上学时间
But I'd rather stay here instead
但我还怀念梦境的香甜
Hey, hey
School is calling, school is calling
上学太急 上学太急
My hair's a disaster, don't know what to do
我披头散发 不知该怎么办
But I need to move faster to make it through
但我必须抓紧 往学校赶
This crazy morning has got me confused
周一的早晨让我手忙脚乱
Clock is racing, time is wasting
分秒必争 耽搁不起
Mind's in circles, brain is spacing
打开大门 暴雨来袭
Everywhere that I go
无论走到何地
Everything that I do
万事都不顺利
I can't shake these Monday blues
周一的阴郁总挥之不去
'Cause some days, I can't find a way
有时候 我处处碰壁
Out of this haze, hope I'll be okay
苦苦等待 只求好运气
Just can't seem to get it right
什么都不如意
A cloud is hanging over me
心情像天空一样阴郁
Hey
Rain is falling, rain is falling
狂风骤雨 狂风骤雨
I wish it was the weekend
我期待周末假期
'Cause you know that's where I'd rather be
就能随心所欲做自己
Hey, hey
Friday's calling, Friday's calling
期待假期 期待假期
I wonder what things won't go my way
为什么总是我倒了霉
Or if I'll ever make it through the day
这样的日子该如何面对
I hope this feeling won't lead me astray
只希望我不会被心情击溃
You'll get through it, you can do it
拿出勇气 相信自己
With your gals, there's nothing to it
姐妹一起 不惧风雨
Everywhere that I go
无论走到何地
Everything that I do
万事都不顺利
I can't shake these Monday blues
周一的阴郁总挥之不去
'Cause some days, I can't find a way
有时候 我处处碰壁
Out of this haze, hope I'll be okay
苦苦等待 只求好运气
Just when I feel like it might come crashing down
每当感觉自己内心很绝望
turn my mood around!
I can count on my friends to help me
朋友们的鼓励能让我重拾正能量
With my gals, there's nothing to it!
姐妹一起 不惧风雨
Everywhere that I go
无论走到何地
With everything that I do
万事都会变顺利
I'll say goodbye to the Monday blues
周一的阴郁即将离我而去
'Cause I've got my friends with me
跟朋友在一起
And the sunshine is all I see
让阳光照亮我心底
Everywhere that I go
无论走到何地
With everything that I do
万事都会变顺利
The world feels so fresh and new
世界到处是新鲜惊喜
'Cause I've got my friends with me
跟朋友在一起
And those blues are ancient history!
周一的阴郁已成过去